I've seen the devil Down sunset
In every place In every face
Yeah, yeah Tell me do you see her?
She's living her life Even if she acts like she
Don't want her love night But if you knew it
She lives her life She calls her paparazzi
Then she acts surprised Oh, oh, oh, oh
I know what she needs, oh She just want the fame
I know what she thinks, oh Give her life of days
Running back to me, oh Put it in her face
Pray it's all to keep, oh Every night, every night
She breaks the sky Flash and light
It's all she ever wants to do
Taking on the needs to be popular
Back to the dream to be popular Kill anyone to be popular
Sell and sold to be popular Popular
Just to be popular Everybody scream cause she popular
She mainstream cause she popular Never be free cause she popular
Money on top of me, money on top of her Money on top of me, money on top of her
You barely fool with me cause you know I'm popular You barely fool with me cause you know I'm popular
I know that you see me Time's gone by
Spend my whole life running from your flashing lights
Try to own it But I'm alright
You can't take my soul without a fucking fight
Oh, oh I know what she needs, oh She just want the fame
I know what she thinks, oh Give her life of days
Running back to me, oh Put it in her face
Pray it's all to keep, oh Every night, every night
She breaks the sky Flash and light
It's all she ever wants to do
Taking on the needs to be popular Back to the dream to be popular
Sell and sold to be popular Popular
Just to be popular Everybody scream cause she popular
She mainstream cause she popular Never be free cause she popular
Money on top of me, money on top of her Money on top of me, money on top of her
You barely fool with me cause you know I'm popular You barely fool with me cause you know I'm popular
Eating it and banging it and keeping it I'm getting canned and I'm kicking it
Money on top of me, money on top of her You barely fool with me cause you know I'm popular
Pop popular, born to be popular She ain't that 20 mil but she running up
She can never be broke cause she popular Tell my wife Cam'on for the followers
Faking on her knees to be popular Back to the dream to be popular
Kill anyone to be popular Sell and sold to be popular
Just to be popular Everybody scream cause she popular
She mainstream cause she popular Never be free cause she popular
Thanks for watching!