I've seen the devil down sunset In every place, in every face
Tell me do you see her?
She's living her life Even if she acts like she don't want a lot
But if you knew her, she lives a lie She goes up paparazzi, then she acts surprised
Oh, oh, I know what she needs She does what the fame, I know what she thinks
Give it like the taste, run it back to me Put it in the face, pray it's all took people
Ooh, every night, every night She breaks in the sky
Fashion lights, it's all she ever wants to do
Faking underneath, tell me popular Better drink, tell me popular
Kill anyone, tell me popular Sell a soul, tell me popular
Popula, just tell me popular Everybody scream, cause she popular
She mainstream, cause she popular Never be free, cause she popular
Money on top of me, money on top of her Money on top of me, money on top of her
You're ready for the me cause you know I'm popular You're ready for the me cause you know I'm popular
I know that you see me, time's gone by Spent my whole life running from your flashing lights
Try to own it, but I'm alright You can't take my soul without a fucking fight
Oh, oh, I know what she needs She does what the fame, I know what she thinks
Give it like the taste, run it back to me Put it in the face, pray it's all took people
Ooh, every night, every night She breaks in the sky
Fashion lights, it's all she ever wants to do
Faking underneath, tell me popular Better drink, tell me popular
Kill anyone, tell me popular Sell a soul, tell me popular
Popula, just tell me popular Everybody scream, cause she popular
She mainstream, cause she popular Never be free, cause she popular
Money on top of me, money on top of her Money on top of me, money on top of her
You're ready for the me cause you know I'm popular You're ready for the me cause you know I'm popular
Run it in run it in, I'm keeping it I'm getting canned, I'm keeping it
Money on top of me, money on top of her Flying through the me cause you know I'm popular
Popula, hold up fall the power, she ain't up 20 man cause she all runn it up
She can never be broke cause she popular Tell her I came off, I'm fall the power
Faking underneath to be popular That's a dream to be popular
Kill anyone to be popular Sell them soul to be popular
Just to be popular Everybody scream coz she popular
She been strange coz she popular Never be free coz she popular