I've seen the devil down sunset in every place and every face.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Tell me, do you see her?
She's living her life.
Even if she got us like she don't want them all night.
But if you knew her, she lives alive.
She goes up a barber, I see then she acts surprised.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
I'm trying to own it, let it all right
You can't take my soul without a fucking fight
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I know what you need, oh, oh, oh
She just will play it, I know what you need
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Give a look to you, it's trying to make me
I'm putting in a face, but you're so incapable
Ooh, baby, not anything
She's based in the sky, oh, fashion lies
Is all she ever wants is
Freaking underneath, took me back it up
Bad to dream, took me back it up
Feeling you on, took me back
Sailing, solved, took me back it up
I'll be with you, just took me back it up
Everybody's screaming, she got me up
She made him scream, push it up, yeah
Never be free, but she got me alive
Anybody who's out for me, when you on top of her
Bad to fall, make you on top of her
I'm standing for a little me, cause you're not a bad one
I'm walking up, I'm on to be my blood
She ain't there, 20 a man, but she's running up
She can never be broke, cause she's not a blood
She can never get off for the following
Faking on the knees, took me back it up
That's a dream, took me back it up
Kill anyone, took me back it up
Tell them, so I'll tell me back it up
I'll be with you, just took me back it up
Everybody's screaming, cause she got me up
She ain't been screaming, cause she back it up
She ain't been free, cause she back it up