Thanks for watching!
I do the same, Think I told you that I never would
I told you I'd change, Even when I knew I never could
Know that I can't find nobody else as good as you
I need you to stay, need you to stay, hey, hey
I get drunk, wake up, I'm wasted still
I realize the time that I wasted
I feel like you can't feel the way I feel
I'll be fucked up if you can't be right, yeah
RM!
Oh-Oh Ohh-Oh
Oh-oh-Oh
I'll be fucked up if you can't be right, yeah
I do the same, Think I told you that I never would
I told you I'd change, Even when I knew I never could
Know that I can't find nobody else as good as you
I need you to stay, need you to stay, hey, hey
I do the same, Think I told you that I never would
I told you I'd change, Even when I knew I never could
If not nobody else as good as you
When I'm away from you I miss your touch
You're the reason I believe in love
It's been difficult for me to trust
And I'm afraid that I'ma fuck it up
Ain't no way that I could leave you stranded
Cause you ain't never left me empty handed
And you know that I know that I can't live without you
So baby stay
Ohh oh ohh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
I'll be fucked up if you can't be right here
I do the same Thing I told you that I never would
I told you I'd change Even when I knew I never could
No, that I can't I'm nobody else as good as you
I need you to stay I need you to stay
Yeah
I do the same Thing I told you that I never would
I told you I'd change Even when I knew I never could
Got nobody else as good as you
I need you to stay, I need you to stay