Michael ignore u
I do the same thing I told you that I never would
I told you I'd change even when I knew I never could
Know that I can't find nobody else as good as you
I need you to stay, need you to stay, yeah
I get drunk, wake up, I'm wastin' still
Realize the time that I wasted
I feel like you can't feel the way IRF
I'll be fucked up if you can't be right
I do the same thing I told you that I never would
I told you I'd change even when I knew I never could
Know that I can't find nobody else as good as you
I need you to stay, need you to stay, yeah
I do the same thing I told you that I never would
I told you I'd change even when I knew I never could
Know that I can't find nobody else as good as you
I need you to stay, need you to stay, yeah
When I'm away from you, I miss your touch
You're the reason I believe in love
It's been difficult for me to trust
And I'm afraid that I'ma fuck it up
Ain't no way that I can leave you stranded
Cause you ain't never let me empty-handed
And you know that I know that I can't live without you
So baby stay
I'll be fucked up if you can't be right
I do the same thing I told you that I never would
I told you I'd change even when I knew I never could
Know that I can't find nobody else as good as you
I need you to stay, need you to stay, yeah
I do the same thing I told you that I never would
I told you I'd change even when I knew I never could
Know that I can't find nobody else as good as you
I need you to stay, need you to stay, yeah