PM
I do the same thing I told you that I'll never will
I told you I changed Even when I know I never could
Know that I can't find nobody else as good as you
I need you to stay, can you to stay?
I can't strong, wake up, I'm wasted
I realized it's time that I'm wasted
I feel like you can't feel the way I will
Be fucked up if you can be right
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I do the same thing I told you that I'll never will
I told you I changed Even when I know I never could
Know that I can't find nobody else as good as you
I need you to stay, can you stay?
I do the same thing I told you that I'll never will
I told you I changed Even when I know I'm never could
Know that I can't find nobody else as good as you
I need you to stay, can you stay?
When I'm away from you I miss your touch
Your threes and I believe a love
It's been difficult for me to trust
And I'm afraid that I'm a fuck it up
And I wait that I can leave you stranded
Cause you ain't never let me empty
Hand it, and you know that I know that I can fit without you
So conditioned that you won't find nothing
And I never could find nobody else as good as bulging
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
What you did, there was no other reason
I'm gonna try, I'm gonna try
I think I told you that I'm never one
I told you I tried
She know when I knew I never could
Know that I can't
It's time nobody else is good
Is you how to use
Can you stay?
I'm gonna try, I'm gonna try